Guide to the Louise Morgan and Otto Theis Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Oversize, 1907-64; 1.75; (1 box)
  - SUBJECT FILES
    - Freud, Sigmund: clipping (Box 39, Folder 934)
    - Garvin, J. L. Garvin, Viola, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 935)
    - Lowenfeld, Margaret, 1945 (Box 39, Folder 936)
    - Pollock, Benjamin, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 937)
    - Stachan, W. J., n.d. (Box 39, Folder 938)
  - PROFESSIONAL PAPERS
    - Morgan Literary Papers
      - Research and Background Material
        - Other printed works, 1950s-60s (Box 39, Folder 939)
    - Theis Literary Papers
      - Book Reviews
        - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 940)
  - NANCY CUNARD PAPERS
    - Cunard Correspondence
      - Morgan, Louise, 1937-64 (Box 39, Folder 941-43)
      - Theis, Otto
    - Additional Material
      - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 944)
- Restricted Fragile Papers, 0.5; (1 box)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Box 40: Restricted fragile material. Reference surrogates have been substituted in the main files. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
  - Box 1, folders 5, 12, 15, 18 (Box 40, Folder 945)
  - Box 2, folder 25 (Box 40, Folder 946)
  - Box 2, folder 31 (Box 40, Folder 947)
  - Box 2, folder 34 (Box 40, Folder 948)
  - Box 3, folder 52 (Box 40, Folder 949)
  - Box 4, folder 72 (Box 40, Folder 950)
  - Box 5, folder 89 (Box 40, Folder 951)
  - Box 5, folder 90 (Box 40, Folder 952)
  - Box 5, folder 95 (Box 40, Folder 953)
  - Box 7, folders 130, 140 (Box 40, Folder 954)
  - Box 8, folders 147, 150, 152, 160 (Box 40, Folder 955)
  - Box 10, folders 194-99, 207-208 (Box 40, Folder 956)
  - Box 11, folder 230 (Box 40, Folder 957)
  - Box 12, folder 245 (Box 40, Folder 958)
  - Box 13, folder 273 (Box 40, Folder 959)
  - Box 15, folders 323, 334 (Box 40, Folder 960)
  - Box 16, folders 342, 355 (Box 40, Folder 961)
  - Box 18, folders 390, 398 (Box 40, Folder 962)
  - Box 19, folder 422 (Box 40, Folder 963)
  - Box 21, folders 449, 455, 463, 468 (Box 40, Folder 964)
  - Box 22, folders 480, 485, 487, 494, 496, 499, 500, 504, 508 (Box 40, Folder 965)
  - Box 23, folders 520, 533, 534 (Box 40, Folder 966)
  - Box 24, folders 539-40, 546, 550, 554, 557-59, 563, 569-70 (Box 40, Folder 967)
  - Box 25, folders 572, 574, 577, 584, 586, 590, 593, 596-97, 602, 607 (Box 40, Folder 968)
  - Box 26, folders 610, 614, 616, 618, 621-22, 626, 628, 632, 649 (Box 40, Folder 969)
  - Box 29, folders 717-18 (Box 40, Folder 970)
  - Box 36, folder 865 (Box 40, Folder 971)
  - Box 37, folder 897 (Box 40, Folder 972)
  - Box 38, folders 913, 920, 922, 924 (Box 40, Folder 973)